lmbinsurance.com 2011-05-03

# LowerMyBills.com - Privacy Policy

|  | 

Last updated: January 4, 2010

**We Respect Your Privacy**

[](https://seal.verisign.com/splash?form_file=fdf/splash.fdf&type=GOLD&sealid=2&dn=WWW.LOWERMYBILLS.COM&lang=en) At LowerMyBills.com®, your privacy is a top priority for us and we are committed to protecting your privacy online. This Privacy Pledge outlines the steps we've taken to ensure that you have a great experience at LowerMyBills.com, and also provides details on how we treat any personal information you may submit to us.

This Privacy Pledge applies to this website, LowerMyBills.com. . In addition, we may from time to time add new sites that may or may not be listed in this Privacy Pledge. Please note that this policy applies only to the information collected through this website and not to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link. In addition, this policy applies only to information collected by LowerMyBills.com online, not offline. 

**TRUSTe**  
[](https://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.lowermybills.com) LowerMyBills.com. is a licensee of the Truste Privacy Program. LowerMyBills.com adheres to the strict requirements set forth by the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent privacy organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence on the Internet, and is the recognized leader in promoting Privacy Pledge disclosure, informed user consent, and consumer education. Their online seal, or "trustmark" is awarded to websites that adhere to established privacy principles and agree to comply with their established oversight and consumer resolution process. If you have questions or concerns about the TRUSTe Privacy Program, please contact us at [ ](mailto:customercare@lowermybills.com)[Customer Care](mailto:customercare@lowermybills.com). If you have further concerns after you have contacted LowerMyBills.com [Customer Care](mailto:customercare@lowermybills.com), you can contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php) directly. 

**Information Collection and Use**  
We will collect and use personal information about you to respond to your request for products and services offered through this website. We will also collect information in order to notify you about products, services, and other opportunities we think will be of interest to you. The information we collect may be from the following sources:

  * Information provided by you in connection with obtaining quotes for home purchase loans, home refinance loans, or home equity loans. For example, you will be asked to provide your full name, address, telephone number, Social Security Number, and other financial information depending upon your request. 
  * Information provided by you in connection with obtaining a credit card. For example, you may be asked to submit your full name and home address. In some cases, you may also be asked to submit additional personal information once you are linked to the credit card issuer's website. 
  * Information provided by you in connection with obtaining quotes for other products or services such as long distance service, internet access, and insurance. 
  * Information provided by you in connection with obtaining a certain product or service offered by one our business partners. 
  * Information you provide us when you register to receive communications from us (such as your email address). 
  * Information you provide us when you enter promotions or sweepstakes offered by LowerMyBills.com (such as your full name, physical address and email address). 
  * Information you provide us through telephone and web based surveys, customer service correspondence, and general feedback. 
  * Information you provide us when you apply for a job with LowerMyBills.com. 

We also collect demographic information. Demographic information is all other information such as gender, zip code, or any information that is not tied to your personal information. In addition, we might receive information about you from other online or offline sources and may add that information to your existing account. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
We share personal information about you under the following circumstances:  

**Loan Products or Service Requests -** If you submit a request for quotes for a loan product or service offered through this website, we will share the personal information contained in your request form (such as your full name, address, telephone number, property location, self-assessed value, and Social Security Number) with third parties, which include banks, mortgage lenders and brokers, and lead aggregators (collectively, "Lender" or "Lenders") in our client network to process and fulfill your request. In some circumstances, we may obtain additional information about you and/or share that information with Lenders in our network. For example, we may use your Social Security Number, your Year of Birth, or your personal information to obtain your credit report and credit score to help us better match you with Lenders. 

All Lenders in our network have entered into agreements with LowerMyBills.com, and are required to comply with federal and state privacy regulations. By submitting your request to LowerMyBills.com, you understand that Lenders may contact you by telephone (on a recorded line), automated calling, email, or regular mail based on the information you provided to us in order to process and fulfill your request, even if you have opted into the National Do Not Call List administered by the Federal Trade Commission, any state equivalent Do Not Call List, or the Do Not Call List of an internal company. If one of the Lenders contacts you and you wish not to be contacted again by that Lender with respect to your inquiry, then you should specifically make a request to that Lender not to contact you again. Please note that the Lenders may maintain the information you provided whether you elect to use their services.

For a complete list of licenses and disclosures, please click here.

**Credit Card Requests -** If you wish to obtain a credit card, you will be asked to provide your personal information (such as your full name and home address).

**Other Products or Service Requests -** If you submit a request for a product or service other than a loan such as Internet access, insurance or long distance service, you will be asked to provide your personal information (such as your full name, address, telephone number and email address). The personal information you submit is either: collected by LowerMyBills.com and shared with the particular business partner operating the service or providing the product you requested or is provided directly to the business partner. Where the service is operated by one of our business partners, the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information will be subject to that business partners' privacy policy. Our business partners may contact you by telephone, email, or regular mail based on the information you provided to us, even if you have opted into the National Do Not Call List administered by the Federal Trade Commission, any state equivalent Do Not Call List, or the Do Not Call List of an internal company. If one of our partners contacts you by telephone and you wish not to be contacted again by that business partner with respect to your inquiry, then you should specifically make a request to that partner not to contact you again. 

**Vendors -** We sometimes disclose the information we collect to companies that operate various services for us such as marketing distribution, advertising, or certain product functionalities. These vendors only have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, and may not share it with others or use it for any other purpose. 

**Job Postings -** We allow for the online submission of resumes and employment related information. Please note that the information (including personal information) collected through the online job application process on the Career section of our website is not subject to this Privacy Policy. However, we want to assure you that information obtained from our job site will be used solely for the purpose of accepting and evaluating your submission for possible employment and the related purposes described on our Career page. We currently use Wet Feet, an outside third party vendor, to handle our employment related submissions. All personal information collected by Wet Feet is forwarded to LowerMyBills.com for the purpose of recruitment. 

**Affiliate Partners -** Personal and business information submitted through the "Affiliate Program" section of our website is collected by Commission Junction and is subject to Commission Junction's policies and procedures. Please review [Commission Junctions' Privacy Policy](http://www.cj.com/privacy.html) before submitting your personal information.

**Subsidiaries, Parent or Sister Companies -** We may share personal and demographic information about you with our subsidiaries, parent company, or sister companies. For example, we may share your information with Experian, ConsumerInfo.com, ClassesUSA.com or PriceGrabber.com. 

**Aggregate, Non-Personal, or De-identified Information.** We may share aggregated information (i.e., information about you and other customers collectively, but not specifically identifiable to you) and other non-personal, de-identified, or anonymous information we collect with third parties, including affiliates to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our Site and on the websites of third parties. If you would prefer that we do not utilize cookies with your website experience, or would prefer to restrict the use of cookies with network advertising partners, please see the "Offering You Choices" section below.

**As Permitted by Law -** **** We may be required to share your personal information with law enforcement or government agencies in response to subpoenas, court orders, federal/state audits or similar circumstances. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of LowerMyBills.com's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

**Business Transfer** **-** As with any other business, it is possible that LowerMyBills, Inc. in the future could merge with or be acquired by another company. If such an acquisition occurs, the successor company would have access to the information maintained by LowerMyBills.com, including your personal information, customer and business account information, but would continue to be bound by this policy unless you consent otherwise. 

**Advertisements and Third Party Ad Servers**  
You may receive advertisements for LowerMyBills.com from third parties. For instance, when visiting a third party website, you may receive a banner advertisement, a "pop up" window advertising LowerMyBills.com, or a displayed a text link on the third party site. Please note that such advertisements are served by the third party website that you have visited and are not controlled by LowerMyBills.com. In addition, such advertisements may be placed by third party ad servers or ad networks such as DoubleClick. These companies may employ cookies and action tags to measure advertising effectiveness. You may find more information at the website of either the individual ad network or the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

**Cookies and IP Addresses**  
To serve you faster and with better quality, we use "cookies" technology. Cookies are small bits of code, usually stored on a user's computer hard drive, which enable a Website to "personalize" itself for each user. We generally use cookies to reduce the time it takes for pages to load on your computer and to assist with customer tracking. Customer tracking (or "click-stream") data collected by us is used to optimize your experience by learning whether or not you successfully used LowerMyBills.com. Additionally, we may capture click-stream data on some of our partner's websites, limited to the activity involved with the completion of offers listed on our website. This information is used to monitor the performance of our partners. We also may use cookies to deliver targeted advertising on our website, websites owned by our sister companies, or websites of third parties. 

We also keep track of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP Address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.   

**Clear Gifs**  
We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movement of Web users. Clear gifs are not tied to users' personally identifiable information. We also use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails the recipients have opened. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If users would like to opt-out of these emails, please see the Opt-out section within any email you receive from us or unsubscribe from our homepage by clicking here.

**Offering You Choices**  

**Marketing Email Options-** You may register to receive communications from us directly on our website or through a third party. Upon registering, we will periodically send you newsletters and other e-mails with offers and promotions. If you no longer wish to receive these communications, please let us know by sending an email to LowerMyBills.com Customer Care (You may also opt-out by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our emails).

**Refusing Cookies -** We utilize reputable third-party vendors to serve advertisements. If, however, you are not comfortable with cookies, you can adjust the settings within your browser to further prohibit being served a cookie. Please see your specific browser's instructions to perform this task.

The National Advertising Initiative ("NAI") has developed an opt-out tool with the express purpose of allowing consumers to "opt-out" of the targeted advertising delivered by its member networks. You can visit the NAI opt-out page and opt-out of cookie tracking. Please visit the NAI by clicking [here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

**Third Party Advertisers -** Please note that LowerMyBills.com can only control its own mailing list and policies. Third party advertisers that maintain their own mailing lists may send communications that advertise our services, and you may need to contact these parties directly in order to stop receiving their email communications.

**Confidentiality and Security**  
The security of your personal information is very important at LowerMyBills.com and we take a number of steps to safeguard it. For example, we limit access to personal information to those employees or agents who assist us in providing requested products and services to you and maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard personal information about you. 

**Third Party Links**  
This Privacy Pledge applies to all information that you provide to LowerMyBills.com. However, when you visit websites to which LowerMyBills.com links, keep in mind you will be interacting with a third party that operates under its own privacy and security policy. If you choose to obtain certain services through a third party site, the data collected by the third party is governed by that third party's privacy policy. A third party site will also have its own policy regarding the use of cookies and clear gifs. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services.

**Framing**  
In some cases, we may use third parties to operate portions of the LowerMyBills.com website. Although the particular section of the website may have a similar appearance as the LowerMyBills.com site, information submitted through these outside third parties are subject to that company's privacy policy unless otherwise stated. For example, personal information submitted through our Affiliate Program is subject to the Commission Junction privacy policy.

**A Special Note about Children's Privacy**  
You must be at least 18 years old to use this website. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, you can use the services offered on our website only in conjunction with your parents or guardians. Please see our Terms of Use for more information. 

**Removing Your Information**  
Federal and state regulations require that we maintain all information (including your personal information) submitted through the LowerMyBills.com website for various time periods. In order to comply with these regulations, we cannot delete your information from our database.

**Questions and Suggestions**  
If you have any questions, concerns or suggestions about our Privacy Pledge, you may contact us: 

By sending an email to:  

By sending a letter to:  
LowerMyBills.com.   
Attn: Customer Care   
4859 W Slauson Ave #405  
Los Angeles, CA 90056

**Changes to this Privacy Pledge**  
LowerMyBills.com may update or modify this Privacy Pledge from time to time. If there are material changes to this Privacy Pledge or in how LowerMyBills.com will use your personal information, we will post such changes here. You will be notified if any of the material changes that affect the use of your personal information and asked to opt-in to the new use of your personal information. If you do not agree with the changes to how your information will be used, please do not continue to use this website.

By using this site, you signify your assent to the LowerMyBills.com Privacy Pledge. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use any of the LowerMyBills.com site. W hen you request rate quotes or other information through LowerMyBills.com, you are authorizing us to share information with our business partners, who will contact you by phone, email, or mail. If you do not want further communication from them, please notify the partner directly. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check the policy each time you use our website to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our Privacy Pledge will indicate the date it was last updated. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Privacy Pledge.

|
